Cut.
-Cut. Let's take a break.
-Okay.
Are you tired?
The shoot is not done yet.
Hold on a little longer.
I need to take a break.
Please.
Mom.
[The late Kim Joowon]
Hello everyone, I'm Jung Yihyun.
[Hello everyone, I'm Jung Yihyun...]
Starting today...
Gah.
I only came here because I heard
working at a columbarium is easy.
Kang Jae-on?
Over there!
Mr. Jung.
You posted on social media that you're
retiring from the industry—is that real?
Why did you suddenly decide to retire?
Does it have to do
with your mother's passing?
Please say something.
Please give us a statement.
Don't you have anything to say
to your fans?
Please say a few words.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
I'm Jung Yihyun's legal representative,
lawyer Yoo Taeseok.
Please direct all official inquiries
to his agency.
Let's go.
[Hongseok]
[Park Seonghyun]
[Shin Yongseok] [Shin Junseop] [Ha Yosep]
[Play Me]
This place hasn't changed at all.
[The Mermaid Prince]
[To K, this script is written for you.]
[Five years ago]
Ah.
Jung Yihyun.
Since he's a celebrity,
I hung out with him a few times,
but he's actually pretty boring.
[To K, this script is written for you.]
Are you still thinking about him?
[Manager Seho-hyung]
Hello, Hyung.
Did you find a painter?
Take this off.
Just paint all of this side.
If you have any questions
or need anything,
feel free to tell me anytime.
Okay, got it.
Also, make sure you leave work on time.
If you ever run into the theater owner,
you'll be fired immediately.
Okay, I understand.
But...
Why? Why can't I run into the owner?
Ah, could it be that this owner is...
a bit abnormal?
Huh?
Ah, yes.
He's crazy.
So you definitely shouldn't run into him.
Got it?
Understood.
I've already told
the painter to leave work on time.
You should also be careful
not to run into him.
If people find out you're doing this
after announcing your retirement,
it'll definitely cause a huge uproar.
I know. I'll be careful.
I know you originally wanted
to be a director,
so I'm helping you out.
But after you're done with this,
come back as an actor.
There are so many fans waiting for you.
I'm also...
one of them.
Hyung,
am I being too selfish?
Hello, Hyung.
Why did you suddenly
ask me to get a massage?
Seho told me.
That you haven't been
sleeping well lately.
So I thought you could relax
and get some sleep.
That's true.
Just enjoy the massage.
I need to take a call.
I'm coming in.
It must hurt a lot.
Get out.
What?
I told you to get out.
Stop.
You're nothing if you're not an actor.
Done already?
Working two jobs a day is exhausting.
You work four, so I can't really
complain in front of you.
It's not tiring at all
once you get used to it.
Wow, how did you get used to it?
You said your dream
is to be an actor, right?
Why do you want to be an actor?
I made a promise with someone
to stand on stage together in the future.
Someday,
we must stand on stage together.
Sure.
Thanks to him, I've been able to hold on.
But it's so hard just to see him.
Oh my god.
It's Jung Yihyun.
The customer you just served
is Jung Yihyun.
I was wondering
what he'd do after retiring.
I didn't expect to see him here.
Wh-What did you say?
He retired.
Didn't you know?
[Actor Jung Yihyun Announces Retirement...
Ending His Acting Career]
The person I met on the roof...
was Jung Yihyun?
Sorry, Kimchi. You must be hungry.
How could you just leave
without saying a word? I was so worried.
Sorry, Hyung.
You don't sound right.
Did something happen?
It's about Kimchi.
I'm thinking about sending him
to a better place.
Now that my mom is gone,
I'm not confident
I can take good care of him.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Hyung.
Maybe my mom was right—
if I'm not an actor, I'm really nothing.
I've already found a pet sitter.
I know you're busy
and can't take care of Kimchi,
so you don't need to worry.
So, stop overthinking.
Understood?
Thank you.
[Pet Sitter Guidelines]
Pet Sitter Guidelines.
One,
[1. Must Poop Outside]
the dog must poop outside.
Two,
beware of mites.
[2. Beware of Mites]
Avoid grassy areas.
[2. Beware of Mites
(Avoid Grassy Areas)]
Three,
keep the leash short.
[3. Keep Leash Short]
[3. Keep Leash Short
(Might Lose the Dog Suddenly)]
You might lose the dog suddenly.
You look like a puppy.
I guess I do.
Yeah.
Slow down.
Paw.
Other paw. That's right. Good boy.
We're planning to build
a fake wall over there.
The back needs to be painted.
But the space is a bit cramped,
so please be careful.
[I took Kimchi for a walk, and gave him a bath.
I had some time left, so I tidied up the house and made a quick meal.
I just thought you might be tired, so I decided to be a little nosy.
Make sure to eat. Food is fuel, after all.]
I took Kimchi for a walk,
and gave him a bath.
I had some time left,
so I tidied up the house,
and made a quick meal.
I just thought you might be tired,
so I decided to be a little nosy.
Make sure to eat.
Food is fuel, after all.
Thank you.
Say something.
How much money did you make?
Probably enough to buy a car, right?
You are dating that guy
you're filming with, right?
That's what the internet says.
Hey!
That's what friends are for.
Just let us take a picture.
If we take a funny picture of you,
we'll get a million followers.
That's enough.
If you have nothing better to do,
you might as well help me clean.
Who wants to help? Raise your hand.
Hey, let's go.
I did great, right?
Wasn't it super cool?
You're like a puppy.
What?
A puppy?
Hey!
Wait for me!